Since the fetch weather task is in the fragment, the
menu option to trigger that task should be inside the fragment
too. That means we should create a new menu layout
for the fragment and we'll call it forecastfragment.xml. The file will
live within the menu folder under the Resources directory. Inside
that file, we'll declare the new menu option for refresh and
give it this menu item ID. We'll also need to define
a string label for this word, Refresh. We're taking this one
step at a time, so just make the menu xml
file change in this exercise. If you compile and run
the app, there'll be no visible change. It won't show
up on the device yet because we haven't inflated the menu
item. Inflating it will be in the coding test after
this. See how the menu main.xml is implemented as an
example. For an additional hint, see the menu training guide
below. When you're done, you can click on this box here.